Western Federation of Miners International Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers Records 5268
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Scovill Manufacturing Company - "The Bulletin", 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.32:no.15 (1948:Aug. 2). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 6: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.32:no.16 (1948:Aug. 16). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 7: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.32:no.17 (1948:Sept. 6). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 8: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.32:no.18 (1948:Sept. 20). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 9: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.32:no.19 (1948:Oct. 4). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 10: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.32:no.20 (1948:Oct. 18). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 11: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.32:no.21 (1948:Nov. 1). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 12: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.32:no.22 (1948:Nov. 15). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 13: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.32:no.23 (1948:Dec. 6). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 14: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.32:no.24 (1948:Dec. 20). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
- Scovill Manufacturing Company - "The Bulletin", 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  January--July 1949
  - Item 1: The Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.33:no.1 (1949:Jan. 3). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 2: The Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.33:no.2 (1949:Jan. 17). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 3: The Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.33:no.3 (1949:Feb. 7). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 4: The Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.33:no.4 (1949:Feb. 21). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 5: The Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.33:no.5 (1949:Mar. 7). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 6: The Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.33:no.6 (1949:Mar. 21). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 7: The Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.33:no.7 (1949:Apr. 4). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 8: The Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.33:no.8 (1949:Apr. 18). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 9: The Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.33:no.9 (1949:May 2). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 10: The Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.33:no.10 (1949:May 6). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 11: The Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.33:no.11 (1949:June 6). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 12: The Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.33:no.12 (1949:June 20). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 13: The Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.33:no.13 (1949:July 4). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 14: The Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.33:no.14 (1949:July 18). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
- "American Metal Market", Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Responsibility For Communists, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Author: American Metal Market
    Notes: Reprinted from American Metal Market v.54:no.167 (1947:Aug. 28)
  - Item 2: An Answer Is Needed, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Notes: Reprinted from American Metal Market v.54:no.191 (1947:Oct. 2)
  - Item 3: The International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Notes: Reprinted from American Metal Market v.54:no.231 (1947:Dec. 3)
  - Item 4: The International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Notes: Reprinted from American Metal Market v.54:no.231 (1947:Dec. 3). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: June 30th And The IUMMSW, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Notes: Reprinted from American Metal Market v.55:no.92 (1948:May 13)
  - Item 6: IUMMSW Is Afraid To Let The Rank And File Decide, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Notes: Reprinted from American Metal Market v.55:no.214 (1948:Nov. 6)
- American Mining Congress, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Labor Legislation, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Author: Charles R. Kuzell
    Notes: February 11, 1947. Statement Before the Senate Committee on Labor and Public Welfare
  - Item 2: Satement of Howard I. Young, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Author: Howard I. Young
    Notes: Februaray 21, 1947. Statement Before the House Committee on Education and Labor
  - Item 3: In Re: S. 2386: Amendment of the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Notes: April 22, 1948. Statement Before a Subcommittee of the Senate Committee on Labor and Public Welfare
- "The Bingham Bulletin", 1907; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Bingham Canyon, Utah. June 14, 1907
  - Item 1: The Bingham Bulletin, 1907; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Author: The Bingham Bulletin
    Notes: v.17:no.4 (1907:June 14). Special issue devoted to the affairs of the W.F.M. Photocopy on 16 large sheets.
- "The People's Voice", 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Helena, Montana. August 9, 1946.
  - Item 1: The Peoples Voice, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Author: The Peoples Voice
    Notes: v.7:no.36 (1946:Aug. 9).
- "The People's Voice", 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Helena, Montana. June 6, 1952
  - Item 1: The Peoples Voice, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Notes: v.13:no.27 (1952:June 6).
- "The Producers News", 1928; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Plentywood, Montana. October 19, 1928
  - Item 1: The Producers News, 1928; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Author: The Producers News
    Notes: v.11:no.29 (1928:Oct. 19). Issue devoted largely to the activities of U. 8. Senator Burton K. Wheeler of Montana.
- "The Searchlight", 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Salt Lake City, Utah. February 15, 1946
  - Item 1: The Searchlight, 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Author: The Searchlight
    Notes: v.6:no.6 (1945:Nov. 2). A Specialist in Neglected Truth. Issue devoted largely to labor topics, in particular the western mining Industry.
  - Item 2: The Searchlight, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.6:no.11 (1946:Jan. 25). A Specialist in Neglected Truth. Issue devoted largely to labor topics, in particular the western mining Industry.
  - Item 3: The Searchlight, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.6:no.12 (1946:Feb. 15). A Specialist in Neglected Truth. Issue devoted largely to labor topics, in particular the western mining Industry.
- "The Searchlight", 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Salt Lake City, Utah. March 29, 1946
  - Item 1: The Searchlight, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Notes: v.6:no.13 (1946:Mar. 29). A Specialist in Neglected Truth. Issue devoted largely to labor topics, in particular the western mining Industry.
  - Item 2: The Searchlight, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Notes: v.6:no.14 (1946:Apr. 19). A Specialist in Neglected Truth. Issue devoted largely to labor topics, in particular the western mining Industry.
- News Clippings, 1893-1950 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  1893, 1917, 1942, 1944-1950. This file of news clippings begins with a front page of the "Butte Bystander" of May 27, 1893 describing the formation of the WFM and continues thru 1952 with coverage of several general topics.
- Periodical Articles, 1947-1952 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  1947-1949, 1952
  - Item 1: Communists Still Threaten Metal-Mine Labor Relations, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Author: Joseph M. Gambatese
    Notes: In Engineering and Mining Journal: v.150:no. 4. (1949:Apr.) pp. 68-71.
  - Item 2: Why Deal With A Union influenced By Communists?, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Notes: In Engineering and Mining Journal: v.149:no.5 (1948:May). pp. 74-79.
  - Item 3: The Taft-Hartley Act and The Mining Industry, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Author: Charles R. Kuzell; Frank J. Ryley
    Notes: Reprint from Mining Congress Journal, December 1947 and January 1948.
  - Item 4: Taft -Hartley and the Miner, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Author: Engineering and Mining Journal
    Notes: In Engineering and Mining Journal: v.148:no.12 (1947:Dec). pp. 52-57.
  - Item 5: Union War in Bessemer, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Author: The Reporter
    Notes: v.1:no.6 (1949:July 5) pp. 12-14.
  - Item 6: Manpower, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Author: Stephen W. Wood
    Notes: February 1952. Reprint
- Bureau of Mines - Copper Mining (Productivity), Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Technology, Employment, And Output Per Man In Copper Mining, 1940; Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Author: T. S. Leong; J. C. Burritt; O. E. Kiessling; C. E. Nighman; George C. Heikes
- Bureau of Mines - Mineral Market Reports, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Mineral Market Reports: Metal Mining In the Central States, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Author: A. J. Martin
    Notes: MMS no.1363 (1946:Jan. 16)
  - Item 2: Mineral Market Reports: Metal Mining In Arizona, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Author: C. E. Needham; Paul Luff
    Notes: MMS no.1364 (1946:Jan. 18)
  - Item 3: Mineral Market Reports: Metal Mining In Idaho, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Notes: MMS no.1365 (1946:Jan. 18)
  - Item 4: Mineral Market Reports: Metal Mining In Montana, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Notes: MMS no.1366 (1946:Jan. 21)
  - Item 5: Mineral Market Reports: Copper in 1945: Preliminary Report, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Author: Helena M. Meyer; Charles White Merrill
    Notes: MMS no.1367 (1946:Jan. 18)
  - Item 6: Mineral Market Reports: Metal Mining In Colorado, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Author: George E. Woodward; S. A. Gustavson
    Notes: MMS no.1368 (1946:Jan. 23)
  - Item 7: Mineral Market Reports: Metal Mining In New Mexico, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Notes: MMS no.1369 (1946:Jan. 22)
  - Item 8: Mineral Market Reports: Metal Mining In Texas, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Notes: MMS no.1370 (1946:Jan. 22)
  - Item 9: Mineral Market Reports: Metal Mining In Wyoming, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Notes: MMS no.1371 (1946:Jan. 22)
  - Item 10: Mineral Market Reports: Metal Mining In California, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Author: Alfred L. Ransome
    Notes: MMS no.1374 (1946:Jan. 24)
  - Item 11: Mineral Market Reports: Metal Mining In Oregon, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Notes: MMS no.1375 (1946:Jan. 24)
  - Item 12: Mineral Market Reports: Metal Mining In Nevada, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Notes: MMS no.1376 (1946:Jan. 23)
  - Item 13: Mineral Market Reports: Metal Mining In Washington, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Notes: MMS no.1377 (1946:Jan. 23)
  - Item 14: Mineral Market Reports: Metal Mining In Utah, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Notes: MMS no.1378 (1946:Feb. 4)
  - Item 15: Mineral Market Reports: Mine Production of Lead and Zinc in the United States, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Author: Richard H. Mote; Charles White Merrill
    Notes: MMS no.1379 (1946:Jan. 24)
  - Item 16: Mineral Market Reports: Mine Production of Copper in the United States, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Notes: MMS no.1380 (1946:Jan. 24)
  - Item 17: Mineral Market Reports: Mine Production of Lead and Zinc in the United States, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Notes: MMS no.1379 (1946:Jan. 24). Copy 2.
  - Item 18: Mineral Market Reports: Mine Production of Gold in the United States, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Author: Charles White Merrill
    Notes: MMS no.1381 (1946:Jan. 30)
  - Item 19: Mineral Market Reports: Lead Industry in 1945: Preliminary, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Notes: MMS no.1382 (1946:Jan. 28)
  - Item 20: Mineral Market Reports: Mine Production of Silver in the United States, 1945: Preliminary Annual Figures, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Notes: MMS no.1383 (1946:Jan. 28)
  - Item 21: Mineral Market Reports: Zinc Industry in 1945: Preliminary, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Author: Richard H. Mote; Esther B. Miller; Charles White Merrill
    Notes: MMS no.1387 (1946:Feb. 8)
- Bureau of Mines - Minerals Yearbook Reprints, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  1944 Yearbook. Reprinted in 1945.
  - Item 1: Gold, Silver, Copper, Lead and Zinc in Montana (Mine Report), 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Author: George E. Woodward; Paul Luff
    Notes: Chapter (preprint) from Minerals Yearbook 1944.
  - Item 2: Gold, Silver, Copper, Lead and Zinc in Utah (Mine Report), 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Gold, Silver, Copper, Lead and Zinc in New Mexico (Mine Report), 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Author: Richard H. Mote
  - Item 4: Gold, Silver, Copper, Lead and Zinc in The Central States (Mine Report), 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: Zinc, 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Author: Alfred L. Ransome; Esther B. Miller
  - Item 6: Copper, 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Author: T. H. Miller; Helena M. Meyer
  - Item 7: Lead, 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 8: Secondary Metals: Nonferrous, 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Author: Herbert L. Cullen
  - Item 9: Gold, Silver, Copper, Lead and Zinc in Nevada (Mine Report), 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 10: Gold, Silver, Copper, Lead and Zinc in Oregon (Mine Report), 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 11: Gold, Silver, Copper, Lead and Zinc in South Dakota and Wyoming (Mine Report), 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 12: Gold, Silver, Copper, Lead and Zinc in New Mexico (Mine Report), 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Notes: Chapter (preprint) from Minerals Yearbook 1944. Copy 2.
  - Item 13: Gold, Silver, Copper, Lead and Zinc in Washignton (Mine Report), 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 14: Gold, Silver, Copper, Lead and Zinc in Texas (Mine Report), 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 15: Gold, Silver, Copper, Lead and Zinc in California (Mine Report), 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 16: Gold, Silver, Copper, Lead and Zinc in Colorado (Mine Report), 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 17: Gold, Silver, Copper, Lead and Zinc in Nevada (Mine Report), 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 18: Gold, Silver, Copper, Lead and Zinc in Idaho (Mine Report), 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 19: Gold, Silver, Copper, Lead and Zinc in Arizona (Mine Report), 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 20: Gold and Silver, 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Author: C. E. Needham
- Bureau of Mines - Nonferrous Scrap Reports, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Nonferrous Scrap Reports: Copper Scrap Consumption Down 8 Percent in December 1945, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Author: Herbert L. Cullen; A. J. McDermid
    Notes: Copper Scrap Consumers Report no.6 (1946:Mar. 15)
  - Item 2: Nonferrous Scrap Reports: Production of Brass Ingot Up 17 Percent in January 1946, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Notes: Copper Scrap Consumers Report no.7 (1946:Apr. 18)
  - Item 3: Nonferrous Scrap Reports: Consumption of Zinc Scrap in December 1945 Maintained November Level, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Notes: Zinc Scrap Consumers Report no.24 (1946:Mar. 1)
  - Item 4: Nonferrous Scrap Reports: Receipts of Lead Scrap at Consumers' Plants Drop in December, But Consumer Consumption Remains High, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Author: Herbert L. Cullen; Edith E. den Hartog; Charles White Merrill
    Notes: Lead Scrap Consumers Report no.24 (1946:Mar. 1)
  - Item 5: Nonferrous Scrap Reports: Nonferrous Scrap Metal Transactions Continue To Decline During December, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Author: Herbert L. Cullen; Helen P. Machall
    Notes: Nonferrous Scrap Consumers Report no.36 (1946:Mar. 1)
  - Item 6: Nonferrous Scrap Reports: Production of Remelt Aluminum Down 7 Percent in December 1945, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Notes: Aluminum Alloy Ingot Monthly Report no.24 (1946:Mar. 8)
- Communist Domination of Unions - Hearings, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
  March/July, 1952
  - Item 1: Communist Domination of Unions and National Security, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Author: U. S. Congress, Senate, Subcommittee of the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare.
    Notes: Hearings. 82nd Cong., 2nd Session, March 17-19, June 6, 11, 13, 17, 19, 27, July 8, 1952.
- Communist Domination of Unions - Report, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
  Part 2 and 4 only
  - Item 1: Report on Communist Domination of Certain Unions: Part II, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Author:. S. Congress, Senate, Subcommittee on Labor and Labor-Management Relations of the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare
    Notes: 82nd Cong., 1st Sess., Document No. 89
  - Item 2: Report on Communist Domination of Certain Unions: Part IV, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Fair Employment Practice Act - Hearing, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
  May 1949
  - Item 1: Federal Fari Employment Practice Act: Hearings to Prohibit Discrimination in Employment because of Race, Color, Religion, or National Origin, 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Author: U. S. Congress, House, Special Subcommittee of the Committee on Education and Labor.. 81st Cong., 1st Sess.
    Notes: May 10-26, 1949.
- United States Tariff Commission, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Mecury, 1944; Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Author: U. S. Tarriff Commission
    Notes: War Changes in Industry Series. Report No. 4
  - Item 2: Magnesium, 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Notes: War Changes in Industry Series. Report No. 10
  - Item 3: Aluminum, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Notes: War Changes in Industry Series. Report No. 14
- Industrial Commission of Colorado, Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Colorado Employnent Relations on Labor Peace Act of 1943, Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
    Author: Industrial Commission of Colorado
- Montana Department of Labor and Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: First Biennial Report of the Department of Labor and Industry: 1913-1914, 1915; Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Author: Montana Department of Labor and Industry.
- Office of Labor National Production Authority, Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Employment in Iron and Copper Mining: Michigan, 1951; Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Author: Office of Labor, National Production Authority
    Notes: (1951?)
- United States Department of Labor, Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Productivity in the Nonferrous Metals Industry: Primary Smelting of Copper, Lead, and Zinc, 1939-48, Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Author: Bernard Michael; Mary L. Kelly
  - Item 2: Manpower Requirements in Metel Mining, 1951; Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Author: Janeece K. Ford
    Notes: Manpower Report no.11 (1951:Oct. 16)
  - Item 3: National Silicosis Conference: Summary Reports Submitted to the Secretary of Labor by Conference Committees, 1937; Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Author: U. S. Department of Labor, Division of Labor Standards
    Notes: Bulletin no.13 (1937:Feb. 3)
  - Item 4: Report on the Bisbee Deportations, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Author: U. S. Department of Labor, President's Mediation Commission
    Notes: November 6, 1917.
  - Item 5: Metal Mines with Manpower Problems in February 1952, Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Author: U. S. Department of Labor, Bureau of Employment Security
  - Item 6: Metal Mining: Iron-Ore, Copper, Lead-Zinc, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Notes: Industry Manpower Servey no.16 (1952:Apr.)
- Campbell, Governor Thomas E., Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The Industrial Battles of 1917, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
    Author: Thomas E. Campbell
    Notes: September 23 and 24, 1918. Summary of Addresses at Bisbee and Globe (Arizona)
- Colorado Political Literature - J.H. Peabody Campaign, 1904; Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Governor Peabody to the Voters: The Colorado Situation Discussed and Misstatements Refuted, 1904; Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Author: J. H. Peabody
    Notes: Supreme Court Decision
  - Item 2: Governor Peabody to the Voters: The Colorado Situation Discussed and Misstatements Refuted, 1904; Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Notes: Supreme Court Decision. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Official Figures, The Real Facts Concerning the Expenditures of the Last Four State Administrations: Democratic Falsehoods Exposed, 1904; Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Communism and Capitalism, Publication (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: A Letter to American Workers, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Author: V. I. Lenin
  - Item 2: Marxism vs. Liberalism: An Interview, 1935; Publication (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Author: Joseph Stalin; H. G. Wells
- Knight, Jesse, Publication (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: The Jesse Knight Family: Jesse Knight, His Forebears and Family, 1941; Publication (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Author: Jesse William Knight
- Labor Turnover, Publication (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Workers on the Move, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 41)
    Author: Kenneth Lehmann; C. Edward Weber
    Notes: ILIR Publications, Bulletin Series v.6:no.1
- Montana Political History (Uncolored History), Publication (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Uncolored History, 1941; Publication (Box 3, Folder 42)
    Author: Frank J. Edwards
- Jansen Correspondence, 1947-1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  1947-1949, 1952. Correspondence with union leaders and various groups and individuals concerned with the history of unionism in the nonferrous metals industry.
- Interviews, 1946-1950 (Box 4, Folder 2)